<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on MonkeyPatch</title>
    <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on MonkeyPatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-FR</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/team/emmanuel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/team/emmanuel/</guid>
      <description>Passionate about technology, new technologies, Technical Leader, Web and mobile architecture</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/team/matthieu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/team/matthieu/</guid>
      <description>Business, Innovation, Strategy and Business Management, Recruitment, Team Management, IU / UX</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/terms/</guid>
      <description>Terms and conditions LEGAL NOTICE By visiting this site, you accept without reservation the following provisions. These provisions may be modified at any time and without notice by the MonkeyPatch team, owner of this site.
SITE OWNER MonkeyPatch Address: 12 avenue de l&amp;rsquo;Europe, 31520 Ramonville Saint-Agne
Telephone: request coordinated by the contact form
SIRET number: 818 973 638 00013
HOSTER Github 88 Colin P Kelly Jr St San Francisco, CA 94107 United States</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A company like no other</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/building/</guid>
      <description>We are challenging the codes of traditional companies.
We want each of our Monkeys to be able to make proposals, be involved in the recruitment of new Monkeys, and have a say in the company&amp;rsquo;s investments. Our employees can take part in the company&amp;rsquo;s board, and thus participate fully in the choice of the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy.
A company that bets on the men in its team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A shared common passion</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/heart/</guid>
      <description>We only recruit engineers who have the IT gene!
The passion for IT and innovation allows our consultants to be always at the forefront of best practices in Web, Mobile and Big Data technologies.
We cultivate this state of mind by devoting time to technological monitoring and the exchange of our expertise.
Being a Monkey invites you to always be involved in the evolution of technologies. But the behaviour and interpersonal skills of our consultants are even more important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/architecture/</guid>
      <description> Architectural design We participate in the development of flexible architectures capable of adapting to the evolution of components and meeting future project challenges.
 Define scalable architectures oriented micro services Comply with safety standards Take into account quality and performance requirements Redesign the existing system to offer flexibility and scalability  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audit and consulting</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/audit/</guid>
      <description> Audit and consulting We support you in the development of the IT strategy at both project and company level.
We also carry out safety, performance or general code review audits in order to recommend areas for improvement and enable you to make the best decisions.
 Assess technical feasibility Cost and plan projects Audit and improve the existing system Propose solutions to strengthen security Recommend areas for improvement to make systems more reliable Help to move towards new working methods  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back-End Expert</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/backend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/backend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;back-end-expert&#34;&gt;Back-End Expert&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MonkeyPatch IT expertise company is looking for Back-End consultants. Are you a technophile and like technical challenges? Would you like to join a dynamic team passionate about IT?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;position-and-missions&#34;&gt;Position and missions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Back-End expert, you are not afraid to immerse yourself in Back End programming languages and databases.
You will have as missions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to back-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propose new features and improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical advice and expertise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be a force of proposal on performance and architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure a permanent monitoring around the uses and technologies in the field of the server and database&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And (depending on missions and experiences) ensure the technical lead of the project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back-end</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/backend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/backend/</guid>
      <description>Without it, many Web or Mobile projects would only be an empty shell. While he often works on elements that are invisible to the user, he can boast of managing their data and security. He is familiar with SQL or NoSQL databases and security concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefit from an attractive and fair remuneration</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/handup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/handup/</guid>
      <description>As a member of the MonkeyPatch team, you will be recognized for your work and commitment, both as an individual and collectively.
We rightly wish to reward all our consultants. Their remuneration includes a fixed salary, individual bonuses linked to their activities and a variable part linked to collective productivity. In our country, salary is neither a taboo nor a secret, we are transparent about the salary of the management team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Consultant</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/bigdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/bigdata/</guid>
      <description> Big Data Consultant Data exploitation is the playground of our BigData consultants who know how to analyze and visualize the quantities of information available to take advantage of it.
 Define strategies for data collection, storage, analysis and visualization Produce accurate data set analysis using the latest technologies Recommend research and modelling techniques  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Expert</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/bigdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/bigdata/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;big-data-expert&#34;&gt;Big Data Expert&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MonkeyPatch IT expertise company is looking for Back-End consultants. Are you a technophile and like technical challenges? Would you like to join a dynamic team passionate about IT?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;position-and-missions&#34;&gt;Position and missions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In love with technology, you have taken the challenge of investing in Data processing projects. Now is the time to capitalize on your experience by working on complex and large-scale projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will perform the following tasks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support our project teams and customers as an Expert in Big Data technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intervene on projects to set up data platforms with high constraints (volumes, processing, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical advice and expertise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure a permanent monitoring around the uses, technologies in the field of BigData and Machine Learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate volume growth rates and set up accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test the analyses and extractions that meet the most common needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building your future as a team</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/team/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re nothing without team spirit!
Invested over the long term, we establish a close relationship with our employees through regular and ongoing exchanges.
We build a bond of trust and commitment that allows us to stimulate the sharing of experience and expertise between Monkeys during afterwork, hackathon,&amp;hellip; or simply over a coffee.
Pushing back its technical limits thanks to the support of a team of experts and the support of a company like no other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev-Ops</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/devops/</guid>
      <description>The missing link between the developer and the system administrator, it improves the performance and security of information systems. It is able to configure any application, regardless of language and server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Consultant</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/devops/</guid>
      <description> DevOps Consultant Our DevOps consultants are specialists in automating development processes including test optimization, continuous integration implementation, automated deployments.
 Implement tools to optimize development Limit manual errors Linking development and operations Manage the security of environments  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Expert</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/devops/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;devops-expert&#34;&gt;DevOps Expert&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MonkeyPatch IT expertise company is looking for Back-End consultants. Are you a technophile and like technical challenges? Would you like to join a dynamic team passionate about IT?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;position-and-missions&#34;&gt;Position and missions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a DevOps Expert, you are called upon to carry out development and operational missions. Your dual expertise allows you to create applications that are perfectly adapted to the infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up tools to automate recurring tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the continuous deployment platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propose new ways to improve the performance of development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical advice and expertise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure a permanent monitoring around the uses, technologies in the field of Devops&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/developpement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/developpement/</guid>
      <description> Project development We provide your teams with our development expertise to increase your ability to innovate and industrialize competitive products.
 Develop with adapted programming tools and languages Enhance quality through the application of good practices Produce high-performance code Reduce the time spent correcting problems  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolving in an environment of expertise and innovation</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/light/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/light/</guid>
      <description>Innovative projects: an exciting and challenging environment.
MonkeyPatch advises and carries out projects for its clients on new technologies related to the Web, Mobility and BigData.
No unproductive inter-contracting. We support partner startups on their technical issues. Between two missions you will work on specific issues in a 10 working day cycle.
Your expertise will always be called upon for a technical feasibility study or for the realization of complex functions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert Big Data</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/big-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/big-data/</guid>
      <description>Able to find his way back into the jungle of data, he sets up the collection, analysis and visualization of data and defines algorithms to transform them into usable information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front-End Expert</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/frontend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/frontend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;front-end-expert&#34;&gt;Front End Expert&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MonkeyPatch IT expertise company is looking for Front-End consultants. Are you a technophile and like technical challenges? Would you like to join a dynamic team passionate about IT?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;position-and-missions&#34;&gt;Position and missions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Front-End Expert, you will play a real pivotal role between Design (UX/UI) and Back-End Development.
You will have as missions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to front-end development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propose new features and improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical advice and expertise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be a force of proposal on performance and architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure a permanent monitoring around the uses, technologies in the field of web &amp;amp; mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And (depending on mission and experience) ensure the technical lead of the project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front-end</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/frontend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/frontend/</guid>
      <description>Pivot between Design (UI/UX) and Back-End, it is in charge of creating clear and simple interfaces for the user. Responsive design no longer holds any secrets for him. Juggling between the most recent Javascript libraries, he also excels in HTML5 and CSS layout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/mobile/</guid>
      <description>Always taped to his smartphone, he creates applications by taking care of the details so that the user experience is the most satisfying. He is fluent in one of the Mobile environments (iOS, Android, Windows Phone).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Consultant</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/mobie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/mobie/</guid>
      <description> Mobile Consultant Our Mobile consultants create native applications as well as Mobile versions of websites on the main Android / iOS platforms.
 Keep up with the rapid evolution of mobile technologies Respect material constraints Integrate with remote systems  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Expert</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/jobs/mobile/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;mobile-expert&#34;&gt;Mobile Expert&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MonkeyPatch IT expertise company is looking for Mobile consultants. Are you a technophile and like technical challenges? Would you like to join a dynamic team passionate about IT?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;position-and-missions&#34;&gt;Position and missions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Mobile Expert, you create and deploy native or cross-platform mobile applications.
You will have as missions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to mobile development in Android, iOS or cross platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propose new features and improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical advice and expertise&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be a force of proposal on performance and architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure a permanent monitoring around the uses, technologies in the field of mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And (depending on missions and experiences) ensure the technical lead of the project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pack Monkey</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/pack/</guid>
      <description>At MonkeyPatch, we like to capitalize and see our Experts progress!
We support any initiative that allows our consultants to enrich their expertise and the recognition of their peers:
 Writing technical articles (blog) Participation and/or facilitation of technical conferences (in Toulouse or abroad) Participation and/or organization of hackathons Development of training materials for new technologies  We assume that everyone must contribute their share.
To encourage this approach, we allocate each year a budget and a number of days of availability to attend training courses, conferences or hackathons&amp;hellip; And finally we allow each consultant to choose his material&amp;hellip;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/interventions/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/interventions/project/</guid>
      <description> Efficient implementation of your projects We ensure optimal product quality during all project phases, by implementing continuous integration principles, which facilitates deployments to different environments and thus optimizes development cycles.
 Design and develop custom products Carry out effective project monitoring using a Lean and Agile approach Accelerate development cycles through continuous integration Integrate the notion of IU / UX for optimal ergonomics  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prototype</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/interventions/prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/interventions/prototype/</guid>
      <description> From idea to Prototype Our team has the necessary skills to help you during the ideation and conceptualization phases of your projects up to the implementation of prototypes to assess market needs.
 Help define your products and services Recommend technical solutions Produce Proofs of Concept Develop models and prototypes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start-up spirit</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/rocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/rocket/</guid>
      <description>An operation that stimulates innovation, strengthens team spirit and makes it more responsive.
Empowering and giving freedom to Monkeys allows them to blossom and grow serenely.
Joining us means integrating:
 An entrepreneurial dynamic: everyone is invested in the development of the company A friendly working atmosphere Constant exchanges Anti-routine initiatives,&amp;hellip;  Cultivate the entrepreneurial spirit of its employees, what if that were the startup spirit?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/interventions/accompagnement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/interventions/accompagnement/</guid>
      <description> Personalized support We guarantee on all our missions the pooling of development techniques and methods so that you can have control over your projects. Your teams thus increase their skills and will be able to reuse the knowledge acquired during the realization of future developments.
 Advise when implementing new features Solving complex issues Support the team&amp;rsquo;s skills development Train on technologies and methods  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical leader</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/lead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/offers/lead/</guid>
      <description> Technical leader We define with your teams the best practices to be respected. We enable them to solve technical problems while respecting the defined architecture.
 Maintain a productive work environment Strengthen team collaboration Finding the balance between standardization and innovation Federating teams to ensure the sustainability of the process Carry out the technical follow-up of the project Identify problems and propose solutions  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI/UX</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/ui-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/profiles/ui-ux/</guid>
      <description>Attentive to the latest Web and Mobile trends, its mission is to design pleasant and easy-to-use interfaces so that the user experience is the best possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Consultant</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/expert/profiles/web/</guid>
      <description> Web Consultant (Front-End / Back-End) Our Web consultants are experts in Front-End and/or Back-End development. They are able to create a Web application with high traffic while respecting the imposed standards.
 Provide a design in accordance with the graphic guidelines Ensure optimal performance for reactive application Adapt to your information systems  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work in a committed and respectful company</title>
      <link>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://monkeypatch.gitlab.io/palm-tree/en/careers/assets/hands/</guid>
      <description>Because working in a company that respects its consultants and honours its commitments is priceless!
The commitment of our employees is crucial for the satisfaction of our customers. To become the number one consulting company, we must maintain the same commitment with all our consultants.
The guarantee of our commitments and the respect of all are the key to the success of our company.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>